Finding Aid for the Collection of Underground, Alternative and Extremist Literature LSC.0050
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Organization Materials
  - E
    - Emergency Council on the Crisis in American Foreign Policy, n.p. (Box 90)
    - Emergency Relief Fund, Incorporated. Lansing, Michigan. (Box 90)
    - Emigration And Immigration, n.p. (Box 90)
    - End Poverty in California. Oakland, California. (Box 90)
    - End Poverty League. Los Angeles, California. (Box 90)
    - English League for the Taxation of Land Values. London, England. (Box 90)
    - Environmental Defense Fund, East Setauket. New York, New York. (Box 90)
    - Environmental Fund. Washington, D.C. (Box 90)
    - Environmental Task Force. Washington, D.C. (Box 90)
    - EPPIC (Educate People Protect Innocent Children). Camarillo, California. (Box 90)
    - Erlich-Alter Memorial Conference. New York, New York. (Box 90)
    - Esperanto, n.p. (Box 91)
    - Etgar (Challenge). New York, New York. (Box 91)
    - Eugenics Society of Northern California. Sacramento, California. (Box 91)
    - European War,, n.p., 1914-1918 (Box 91)
    - Evolve. San Diego, California. (Box 91)
    - Expulsion - U.S., n.p. (Box 91)
  - F
    - Fabian International Bureau. London, England. (Box 91)
    - Fact Sheet. Los Angeles, California. (Box 92)
  - G
    - Facts in Review. New York, New York. (Box 92)
      German Library of Information.
    - Fair Housing Council of Santa Monica. Santa Monica, California. (Box 92)
      Note: Includes Southern California material as well.
    - Fair Play for Cuba Committee, n.p. (Box 92)
    - Faith and Freedom Foundation, Incorporated. Arcadia, California. (Box 92)
    - Far Eastern Affairs Pamphlets, n.p. (Box 92)
    - Farm Research. New York, New York. (Box 92)
    - Farm Workers Relief Fund. Delano, California. (Box 92)
      Note: Includes Farm Workers material from other areas as well.
    - FAS (Federation of American Scientists) Newsletter. Washington, D.C. (Box 93)
    - Fascism, n.p. (Box 92)
    - Fascism - Italy, n.p. (Box 92)
    - Fascism - Yugoslavia, n.p. (Box 92)
    - Fascist Confederation of Industrialists, Rome, Italy. (Box 92)
    - Federal Freedom of Information & Privacy Act, n.p. (Box 93)
    - Federal Reserve Corporation, n.p. (Box 93)
    - Federation for Security of Schools. Los Angeles, California. (Box 93)
    - Fellowship for Advancing Inter-Group Relations. Los Angeles, California. (Box 93)
    - Fellowship for Social Justice. Los Angeles, California. (Box 93)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation. New York, New York. (Box 93)
    - Ferrero - Sallitto Defense Conference. New York, New York. (Box 93)
    - Fichte Association (Fichte-Bund). Hamsburg, Germany. (Box 93)
    - Fifth Column, n.p. (Box 93)
    - Fight Inflation Together - F.I.T. Saugus, California. (Box 93)
    - Finland - politics and government, n.p. (Box 93)
    - Fire and Police Research Association of Los Angeles. Fi-Po News, n.p., Note: 1970 - vol.9 no.3-6, 1971 - vol.10 no.1-3,5-8/9. (Box 93)
    - Fitts, Buron Rogers, 1895-, n.p. (Box 93)
    - Focus. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 93)
    - Food contamination, n.p. (Box 93)
    - For America. Washington, D.C. (Box 93)
    - Foreign - miscellaneous - Belgium, n.p. (Box 82)
    - Foreign - miscellaneous - France, n.p. (Box 82)
    - Foreign - miscellaneous - German, n.p. (Box 82)
    - Foreign Languages Publishing House, Moscow, Russia. (Box 82)
    - Foreign Policy Association. New York, New York. (Box 93)
    - Fort Hood Four Legal Defense Committee. New York, New York. (Box 93)
    - Forum Publishers. New York, New York. (Box 93)
    - Forum Publishing Company. Boston, Massachusetts. (Box 93)
    - Foundation for Economic Education, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 93)
    - Free Angela Davis. Los Angeles, California. (Box 95)
    - Free Enterprise Department. Los Angeles, California. (Box 95)
    - Free Grapvine. Los Angeles, California. (Box 95)
      Note: 1970, vol.12 no.2 (November).
    - Free Society Association. Washington, D.C. (Box 95)
    - Free Speech Movement. Berkeley, California. (Box 95)
    - Freedom Club Bulletin. Los Angeles, California. (Box 95)
    - Freedom Draft Movement. Los Angeles, California. (Box 95)
    - Freedom House. New York, New York. (Box 95)
    - Freedom News. Greenville, Texas. (Box 95)
    - Freedom Now Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 95)
    - Freedom of Choice. Los Angeles, California. (Box 95)
    - Freedom Press. Glendale, California. (Box 95)
    - Freedom Press. London, England. (Box 95)
    - Freedom to Read Foundation. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 95)
    - Freedom's Voice. Westminster, California. (Box 95)
    - Freedom. Anarchist Weekly. London, England. (Box 95)
    - Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge, n.p. (Box 95)
    - Freie Arbeiter Stimme. New York, New York. (Box 95)
    - Friends Committee on Legislation. Pasadena, California. (Box 96)
    - Friends Committee on National Legislation. Washington, D.C. (Box 96)
    - Friends of Debs Column. New York, New York. (Box 96)
    - Friends of Europe. London, England. (Box 96)
    - Friends of Fighters for Russian Freedom. New York, New York. (Box 96)
    - Friends of Ireland. Los Angeles, California. (Box 96)
    - Friends of Irish Freedom, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 96)
    - Friends of Poor People's Campaign. Los Angeles, California. (Box 96)
    - Friends of Rhodesia Independence, n.p. (Box 96)
    - Friends of the Abraham Lincolm Battalion. New York, New York. (Box 96)
    - Friends of the First Amendment. New York, New York. (Box 96)
    - Friends of the River. San Francisco, California. (Box 96)
    - Friends of the Soviet Union. New York, New York. (Box 96, Box 97)
    - General Defense Committee. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 97)
    - German American League for Culture, n.p. (Box 97)
    - German Hospital Association (Deutscher Hospital Verein), n.p. (Box 97)
    - German Library of Information. New York, New York. (Box 97)
    - German-American. New York, New York. (Box 97)
    - GI Civil Liberties Defense Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 97)
    - Ginn and Company, n.p. (Box 97)
    - Global Views. San Francisco, California. (Box 97)
    - Good Government Group of Seal Beach. Seal Beach, California. (Box 97)
    - Grand Central Industrial Centre. Glendale, California. (Box 97)
    - Grass Roots. San Angelo, Texas. (Box 97)
    - Grass Roots Publishing Company. San Gabriel, California. (Box 97)
    - Gray Panthers Project Fund. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. (Box 97)
    - Greater East Asia War Inquiry Commission, n.p. (Box 97)
    - Green Power Organization International. Los Angeles, California. (Box 97)
    - Greenpeace, U.S.A. Santa Barbara, California. (Box 98)
    - Group of Friends of Spain. New York, New York. (Box 98)
    - Group Research, Incorporated, n.p. (Box 98)
    - Guerilla. New York, New York. (Box 98)
      Note: 1968 - vol.2 no.2-3.
  - H
    - Ha-orah. Los Angeles, California. (Box 98)
    - Ham and Eggs for Californians. Hollywood, California. (Box 98)
    - Handgun Control, Incorporated. Washington, D.C. (Box 98)
    - Handicap Publications. Hollywood, California. (Box 98)
    - Harlem Trade Union Council. New York, New York. (Box 98)
    - Harry Bridges Defense Committee, n.p. (Box 98)
    - Hawaii Foundation for American Freedoms. Honolulu, Hawaii. (Box 98)
    - Heads Up. San Diego, California. (Box 98)
    - Hearst Strike Committee. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 98)
    - Heatwave. London, England. (Box 98)
    - Herald of Freedom. Zarephath, New Jersey. (Box 98)
    - Hermon-Monterey Hills Association. Los Angeles, California. (Box 98)
    - Hershey Bar, General #1, n.p. (Box 98)
    - Hershey Bar, General #2, n.p. (Box 99)
    - High School Students Against the War. Los Angeles, California. (Box 99)
    - Hollywood Anti-Nazi League, n.p. (Box 99)
    - Hollywood Life, n.p. (Box 99)
    - Hollywood Review. Hollywood, California. (Box 99)
    - Homosexuality, n.p. (Box 99)
    - Howe Social Security Plan. Los Angeles, California. (Box 99)
    - Huey P. Newton Defense Fund, n.p. (Box 99)
    - Hugh Moore Fund. New York, New York. (Box 99)
    - Human Affairs Pamphlets. Hinsdale, Illinois. (Box 99)
    - Human Betterment Foundation. Pasadena, California. (Box 99)
    - Human Events. Washington, D.C. (Box 99)
    - Human Inventory, Incorporated. Los Angeles, California. (Box 99)
    - Human Rights, n.p. (Box 99)
    - Humanism, n.p. (Box 99)
    - Humanist Association. Huntington Park, California. (Box 99)
    - Humanist Friend Publishers. San Diego, California. (Box 99)
    - Humanist World Fellowship of California, Incorporated. Berkeley, California. (Box 99)
    - Humanitas, n.p. (Box 99)
      American Humanist Association.
    - Humanity Guild. New York, New York. (Box 99)
    - Hungarian Freedom Fighters Federation, Incorporated. Los Angeles, California. (Box 99)
    - Hyun, David, n.p. (Box 99)
  - I
    - ICOR. New York, New York. (Box 102)
    - Ideal Community School and Services. Canoga Park, California. (Box 99)
    - In Fact - an Antidote for Falsehood in the Daily Press. New York, New York. (Box 99)
    - Independent Action Association of Compton. Compton, California. (Box 102)
    - Independent American. Littleton, Colorado. (Box 102)
    - Independent Labour Party (Great Britain), n.p. (Box 102)
    - Independent Progressive Party, n.p. (Box 102)
    - Independent Socialist Club, n.p. (Box 102)
    - Independent Socialist Committee. Berkeley, California. (Box 102)
    - Independents of America, n.p. (Box 99)
    - India Famine Relief Committee. New York, New York. (Box 99)
    - Industrial Union Party. New York, New York. (Box 103)
    - Individuals Against the Crime of Silence. Los Angeles, California. (Box 38, 99)
      - Think Black!, undated (Box 38)
    - Indochina Mobile Education Project. Washington, D.C. (Box 99)
    - Indochina Peace Campaign. Los Angeles, California. (Box 99)
    - Indochina Peace Coalition. Los Angeles, California. (Box 99)
    - Indochina Resource Center. Washington, D.C. (Box 100)
    - Industrial Workers of the World, n.p. (Box 101, Box 102)
    - INFACT. Los Angeles, California. (Box 102)
    - Inquiry. Los Angeles, California. (Box 103)
    - Inside Story. Los Angeles, California. (Box 103)
    - Institute for Historical Review. Costa Mesa, California. (Box 103)
    - Institute for International Order. New York, New York. (Box 103)
    - Institute for International Politics and Economics. Prague, Czechoslovakia. (Box 103)
    - Institute for Propaganda Analysis. New York, New York. (Box 103)
    - Institute for Special Research. Pasadena, California. (Box 103)
    - Institute for the Study of Non-Violence. Palo Alto, California. (Box 103)
    - Institute of International Education. New York, New York. (Box 103)
    - Institute of Pacific Relations. New York, New York. (Box 103)
    - Instituto Del Pueblo. Los Angeles, California. (Box 103)
    - Inter-Religious Committee for the Los Angeles Region Goals Project. Los Angeles, California. (Box 109)
    - Intercollegiate League for Industrial Democracy. New York, New York. (Box 103)
    - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists, Incorporated. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. (Box 103)
    - Interfaith Council. Northridge, California. (Box 103)
    - International Bible Students Association. Brooklyn, New York. (Box 103)
    - International Brigade Association. London, England. (Box 103)
    - International Committee of Conscience on Vietnam. New York, New York. (Box 103)
    - International Cooperative Alliance, n.p. (Box 103)
    - International Days of Protest Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 103)
    - International Industrial Relations Institute. Hague, Netherlands. (Box 103)
    - International Labor Defense. New York, New York. (Box 103)
    - International Organization, n.p. (Box 104)
    - International Pamphlets. New York, New York. (Box 104)
    - International Publishers. New York, New York. (Box 104, Box 105, Box 106, Box 107, Box 108)
    - International Rescue Committee. New York, New York. (Box 109)
    - International Review. New York, New York. (Box 109)
    - International School of Peace, n.p. (Box 109)
    - International Services of Information Foundation, Incorporated. Baltimore, Maryland. (Box 109)
    - International Socialist Party, n.p. (Box 109)
    - International Solidarity Committee. New York, New York. (Box 109)
    - International Union of the Revolutionary Theatre. Moscow, Russia. (Box 109)
    - International Workers Order, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 109)
    - International Working Men's Association, n.p. (Box 109)
    - International Youth Commission, n.p. (Box 109)
    - Internationalism, n.p. (Box 109)
    - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity. New York, New York. (Box 109)
    - Iran Hostage Crisis,, n.p., 1979-1981 (Box 109)
    - Irish-American Educational League. San Francisco, California. (Box 109)
    - Isla Vista (California) - riots, n.p. (Box 109)
    - Israel Information Services. New York, New York. (Box 109)
    - Italian Historical Society. New York, New York. (Box 109)
    - Italian Library of Information. New York, New York. (Box 109)
    - Italian Patronati to Aid the Political Prisoners of Italy. New York, New York. (Box 109)
    - Italy - Politics and government, n.p. (Box 109)
  - J
    - Jacoby & Gibbons and Associates. Los Angeles, California. (Box 109, Box 110)
    - Japanese - Americans In Search for Truth (J.U.S.T.). Los Angeles, California. (Box 110)
    - Japanese Chamber of Commerce of New York, n.p. (Box 110)
    - Jefferson School of Social Science. New York, New York. (Box 110)
    - Jeffersonian Democrats of Eleven Western States. Los Angeles, California. (Box 110)
    - Jewish Black Book Committee. New York, New York. (Box 110)
    - Jewish Currents. New York, New York. (Box 110)
    - Jewish Defense League, n.p. (Box 110)
    - Jewish Free Press. New York, New York. (Box 110)
    - Jewish Institute for National Affairs. Washington, D.C. (Box 110)
    - Jewish Labor Committee. New York, New York. (Box 110)
    - Jewish Life. New York, New York. (Box 110)
    - Jewish Orthodox Youth Speaks, Brooklyn. New York, New York. (Box 110)
    - Jewish Peace Fellowship. New York, New York. (Box 110)
    - Jewish People's Committee for United Action Against Fascism and Anti-Semitism. New York, New York. (Box 110)
    - Jewish Peoples Committee, n.p. (Box 110)
    - Jewish Radical Community. Los Angeles, California. (Box 110)
    - Jewish Reconstructionist Foundation, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 111)
    - John Birch Society, n.p. (Box 111)
    - John Dewey Student Unit of the League for Independent Political Action, n.p. (Box 112)
    - John Reed Club, n.p. (Box 112)
    - Johnson-Forest Tendency. New York, New York. (Box 112)
    - JOIN Community Union. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 112)
    - Join Hands. Los Angeles, California. (Box 112)
    - Joint Amnesty Comittee. Washington, D.C. (Box 112)
    - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee. New York, New York. (Box 112)
    - Jubilee Housing, Incorporated. Washington, D.C. (Box 112)
    - Judge Armstrong Foundation. Fort Worth, Texas. (Box 112)
    - June 23rd Movement. Los Angeles, California. (Box 112)
    - Justice For All. Beverly Hills, California. (Box 112)
    - Justice for Cyprus American Committee of San Francsico-Bay Area. Oakland, California. (Box 112)
  - K
    - Kalifat, n.p. (Box 112)
    - Karen Silkwood Fund. Washington, D.C. (Box 112)
    - Keep America Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 112)
    - Keep America Out of War Committee. New York, New York. (Box 112)
    - Kennedy Memorial for Internal Peace. Los Angeles, California. (Box 112)
    - Kent State Due Process of Law Fund. Washington, D.C. (Box 112)
    - Korean Cultural and Freedom Foundation, Incorporated. Washington, D.C. (Box 113)
    - Ku Klux Klan, n.p. (Box 113)
    - Kutcher Civil Rights Defense Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 113)
  - L
    - Labor And Laboring Classes, n.p. (Box 114)
    - Labor And Laboring Classes - Canada, n.p. (Box 115)
    - Labor And Laboring Classes - Great Britain, n.p. (Box 115)
    - Labor And Laboring Classes - Mexico, n.p. (Box 115)
    - Labor Committee for Full Employment. San Francisco, California. (Box 115)
    - Labor Educational Association. New York, New York. (Box 115)
    - Labor Party Association. New York, New York. (Box 115)
    - Labor Party of Cook County. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 115)
    - Labor Party of Illinois. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 115)
    - Labor Research Association. London, England. (Box 115)
    - Labor World. Los Angeles, California. (Box 115)
    - Labor Youth League. New York, New York. (Box 115)
    - Labor's Non-Partisan League. Washington, D.C. (Box 115)
    - Labour Party (Great Britain), n.p. (Box 115, Box 116)
    - Labour Publishing Company Limited. London, England. (Box 116)
    - Labour Research Department. London, England. (Box 116)
    - Laissez-Faire, n.p. (Box 117)
    - Law Students Civil Rights Research Council. New York, New York. (Box 117)
    - Lawyers Committee on American Relations with Spain, n.p. (Box 117)
    - League for Independent Political Action, n.p. (Box 117)
    - League for Labor Palestine. New York, New York. (Box 117)
    - League for Public Interests. Hollywood, California. (Box 117)
    - League of American Writers. New York, New York. (Box 117)
    - League Of Nations, n.p. (Box 117)
    - League of Nations Non-Partisan Association, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 118)
    - League of Professional Groups for Foster and Ford. New York, New York. (Box 118)
    - League to Abolish Capital Punishment. New York, New York. (Box 118)
    - League to Save America First, n.p. (Box 118)
    - LeFevre's Journal. Orange, California. (Box 118)
    - Left Wing Section Socialist Party. New York, New York. (Box 118)
    - Legislative Research Incorporated. Anaheim, California. (Box 118)
    - Leninist League. New York, New York. (Box 118)
    - Lexington Avenue Civic Association, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 118)
    - Liberal Democrat. Berkeley, California. (Box 118)
      Note: April 1961, July 1961, November 1961, May 1962.
    - Liberal Immigration League. New York, New York. (Box 118)
    - Liberalism, n.p. (Box 118)
    - Liberation. New York, New York. (Box 118)
    - Liberator. New York, New York. (Box 118, Box 119)
      Note: Miscellaneous issues only.
      See also ORION catalog: HX 1 L615.
    - Liberator Press. Carson City, Nevada. (Box 119)
    - Libertarian Connection. Los Angeles, California. (Box 119)
    - Libertarian Publishing Society. New York, New York. (Box 119)
    - Libertarian Socialist League. Los Angeles, California. (Box 119)
    - Liberty Amendment Committee of the U.S.A. Los Angeles, California. (Box 119)
    - Liberty Hill Foundation. Santa Monica, California. (Box 119)
    - Liberty Letter. Washington, D.C. (Box 119)
    - Liberty Lobby. Washington, D.C. (Box 119)
    - Library of Suppressed Facts & Controversial Opinions. Hollywood, California. (Box 119)
    - Life Line, n.p. (Box 189)
    - Life Science. San Diego, California. (Box 189)
    - Life Science International. Los Angeles, California. (Box 189)
    - Lobbying, n.p. (Box 189)
    - Long March. Los Angeles, California. (Box 189)
    - Lord's Day Alliance of California, n.p. (Box 189)
    - Los Angeles Citizens' Council. Los Angeles, California. (Box 189)
    - Los Angeles Committee for Defense of the Bill of Rights. Los Angeles, California. (Box 189)
    - Los Angeles Committee to Free Morton Sobell. Los Angeles, California. (Box 189)
    - Los Angeles Committee to Re-open the Rosenberg Case. Los Angeles, California. (Box 189)
    - Los Angeles Emergency Committee to Aid the Strikers. Los Angeles, California. (Box 189)
    - Los Angeles Equalizer. Los Angeles, California. (Box 189)
    - Los Angeles Free Press. Los Angeles, California. (Box 189)
      Note: May 24-30 1968.
    - Los Angeles News Advocate. Sherman Oaks, California., 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
      Folder 1 -- Vol. 1, no. 1 (October 16, 1970) - Vol. 1, no. 12 (September 20 - October 15) Folder 2 -- Vol. 2, no. 2(Novermber 15, 1971) - Vol. 2, no. 19 (August 1- 15, 1972)
    - Los Angeles News and Letters Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 189)
    - Los Angeles Physicians for Social Responsibility. Los Angeles, California. (Box 189)
    - Los Angeles Police Department, n.p. (Box 189)
    - Los Angeles Workers School, n.p. (Box 189)
  - M
    - MADD. Carmichael, California. (Box 189)
    - Makers of Freedom. New York, New York. (Box 189)
    - Man and State. Berkeley, California. (Box 189)
    - Manion Forum. South Bend, Indiana. (Box 189)
    - March on Washington Movement. New York, New York. (Box 189)
    - Markley - Suares Defense Committee. Holyoke, Massachusetts. (Box 120)
    - Marxian Educational Society, Detroit, Michigan. (Box 120)
    - Marxian Philosophical Society, n.p. (Box 120)
    - Marxist - Humanist. Los Angeles, California. (Box 120)
    - Masses & Mainstream, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 120)
    - May 2nd Committee Harvard - Radcliffe, n.p. (Box 120)
    - May 2nd Movement. New York, New York. (Box 120)
    - Medgar Evers Fund. New York, New York. (Box 120)
    - Medical Aid for Vietnam. Cambridge, Massachusetts. (Box 120)
    - Medical Bureau & North American Committee to Aid Spanish Democracy, New York. (Box 120)
    - Medical Committee for Human Rights. New York, New York. (Box 120)
    - Melish Defense Committee, n.p. (Box 120)
    - Mexican American Legal Defense and Educational Fund. Los Angeles, California. (Box 120)
    - Mexican Welfare Committee, Incorporated. Los Angeles, California. (Box 120)
    - Mexico - Politics And Government, n.p. (Box 120)
    - Militant. New York, New York. (Box 120)
      Note: 1961-62, 1968 - miscellaneous issues.
    - Militant Forum. Los Angeles, California. (Box 120)
    - Militant Labor Forum. Los Angeles, California. (Box 120)
    - Militarism, n.p. (Box 120)
    - Minnesota Action Fund, St. Paul, Minnesota. (Box 120)
    - Minority of One, Passaic, New Jersey. (Box 120)
    - Minutemen, n.p. (Box 121)
    - Mississippi Free Press, n.p. (Box 121)
    - Modern Forum Incorporated. Los Angeles, California. (Box 121)
    - Modern Pioneers of America. Los Angeles, California. (Box 121)
    - Modern Quarterly. New York, New York. (Box 121)
    - Modern Uptopian. Berkeley, California. (Box 121)
    - Modern Critique Association, Hong Kong. (Box 121)
    - Moneysworth. New York, New York. (Box 121)
    - Monthly Review. New York, New York. (Box 121)
    - Montrose Newman Company, Incorporated. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 121)
    - Mooney, Thomas J., 1882-1942, n.p. (Box 121)
    - Moral Re-armament, n.p. (Box 121)
    - Morning Freiheit Association. New York, New York. (Box 121)
    - Mother Earth Bulletin. New York, New York. (Box 121)
    - Mother Earth Publishing Association. New York, New York. (Box 121)
    - Mothers' Crusade for Victory over Communism. Pasadena, California. (Box 121)
    - Mott for India. Ithaca, New York. (Box 121)
    - Movement. San Francisco, California. (Box 121)
    - Movement for a Democratic Military. Van Nuys, California. (Box 121)
    - Movement to Impeach Earl Warren. Belmont, Massachusetts. (Box 122)
    - Movimiento Pro-Independencia de Puerto Rico. New York, New York. (Box 122)
    - Mozambican Refugees, Committee to Aid. Hollywood, California. (Box 122)
    - Muhammad's Mosque no.2. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 122)
    - Mutual Real Estate Investment Trust. New York, New York. (Box 122)
  - N
    - Natioanl Assembly for Democratic Rights. New York, New York. (Box 123)
    - National Hands Off Russia Committee. Adelphi, England. (Box 127)
    - National Abortions Rights Action League. Washington, D.C. (Box 123)